mediahitt.com 2017-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Mediahitt.com

PRIVACY POLICY

Digital Access Media LLC (the “Company”) values the importance of protecting your personal information and is committed to protecting your privacy online. Because, the Company understands that you are concerned about your privacy, the Company has instituted policies and security measures intended to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. 

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) describes, among other things, the types of information collected about you when you visit the Company’s website (the “Website”); how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed; how you can control the use and disclosure of your information; and how your information is protected. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

By accessing or using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Website or any of the products, software or services offered or provided by the Company.

  1. Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to information, including contact information, collected about you by the Company. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information collected through any other website. Please note that the Website may contain links to third party websites that are completely unrelated to the Company. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, and the Company further recommends that you visit the privacy policies of each website that you visit.

  2. Information Collected

  1. Information you provide directly to the Company

The Company may ask you for different types of information when you register your account (“Account”) with the Website, including: contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, phone number; user name, password, and password reminder questions and answers; payment and identity verification information, such as credit card number or debit card number.

  2.  Information automatically collected  by the Company

When you are accessing the Website, the Company may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology, including but not limited to: your browser type and operating system; your Internet Protocol (IP) address; software and hardware attributes and your search and page history. This information is used to operate, develop and improve the Website and the products, software and services offered and provided by the Company. 

  3. Information collected by “Cookies”

When you are accessing the Website, the Company, or a third party, including one of the Company’s advertising partners, may send one or more cookies to your computer. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s browser to store your preferences. The Company uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Website. You may select to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off such cookies through your browser settings. You should look at your browser settings to learn the different ways you can control how your browser interacts with cookies. If you choose to disable cookies on your device, some features of the Website may not function properly.

  3. Use of Information

The Company uses the information that you provide or that is collected to: personalize user experience; operate, maintain and improve the Website; improve customer service; process transactions and provide its services;  send administrative communications such as notices of updates to the Website, customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any product, software or service you have downloaded from the Website; understand usage trends and preferences of users; develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests; customize the content you see when you visit the Website; and for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time the Company collects your information or with your consent.

  4. Protection of Information

The Company is committed to protecting your information. The Company has adopted commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical safeguards to help protect your information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. The Company wants you to feel confident using the Website but cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to the Company and you do so at your own risk. Once you transmit your personal information, the Company makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of the Website. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, altered, disclosed or destroyed by breach of any of the Company’s technical, administrative or physical safeguards. 

  5. Disclosure of Information  

The Company is committed to maintaining your trust and wants you to understand when and with whom your information is shared with.

  4. With your consent

With your consent, the Company may share your contact information with third-party marketing partners. 

  5. Authorized third-party service providers

The Company may share your information with third-party vendors who assist the Company with specialized services, including customer support, email and text message deployment, business analytics, marketing, and data processing. These third parties are allowed to use your information to help the Company provide you with its products, software and services and not for any other purpose.

  6. For external processing

The Company may provide personal information to its [affiliates](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/key-terms/#toc-terms-affiliates) or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for the Company, based on the Company’s instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  7. Business transfers 

The Company may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of the Company, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

  8. Legal requirements

The Company may disclose your information, including contact information, in the event that there is good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of the Company, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

  9. Protect the Website and users

The Company may disclose information to protect and defend the legal rights, interests, and safety of the Website, the Company itself and any of its directors, members, employees, agents, licensors, representatives and contractors; and to protect the safety and security of users of the Website as well as members of the public.

  6. Accessing and Updating Information 

You can access your personal information that the Company has collected by logging into your Account under the “My Account” section of the Website. You may also update or amend any of your personal information by logging into your Account or by contacting the Company directly. If you request that your Account be shut-down or your information deleted, the Company will disable your Account within a reasonable period of time. Please note that the Company may need to retain some information about you in order to satisfy its legal and security obligations. For example, some of your information may remain in back-up storage even if you ask the Company to delete it. To protect your privacy and security, the Company will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your Account.

  7. Privacy Protection for Children

IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 13, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE WEBSITE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF THE YOUNG IS ESPECIALLY IMPORTANT. FOR THAT REASON, THE COMPANY DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT OR MAINTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 13. 

  8. Link to Third Party Websites

If you select a link to a third party website from the Website, you will be leaving the Website and any information that you disclose on the third party website will be governed by that website's privacy policy.

  9. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

The Company may update this Privacy Policy periodically without further notice to you, to reflect changes in its practices and service offerings and this will be reflected by a “Last Modified” date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. If the Company makes any material changes in the way it uses your information, it will notify you by sending an email message to the email address you most recently provided or by prominently posting a notice of the changes on the Website.

  10. How to Contact the Company

Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact the Company by telephone at [1-866-949-7187] or by email to [support@mediahitt.com].  The Company will make reasonable efforts to respond to you within a reasonable delay.

Last Modified: June 11, 2017
